Hi everyone and welcome to a new Marimur video here on my channel. I received some new accessories,
harness, lingerie from Marimur and I'm going to show them to you today. Maybe you already know
but Marimur is a Ukrainian brand and this parcel left Kiev a few days before the Russian invasion
started and I received it a few days after there was already fighting in Kiev. So I checked in with
my contact person at Marimur. She's safe. She had to leave Kiev of course and they're all safe but
of course they can't run the business as usual anymore. So if you want to support Marimur, buy
gift cards, order the pieces in stock and support them this way. And I hope they're all safe and
we'll have better time soon. Let's have a look at the first set. It comes in this beautiful red box.
And I'm going to show you bodysuit and a harness combination first. I just have to find it in here.
This is the Helen bodysuit and I'm wearing undies under it because otherwise
not safe for work or for YouTube. And I'm going to put this harness on top of it
which has a black and a red side. So the red side is the inside but I wanted to show
it to you before I'm going to put it on. Full outfit. These are the cuffs and
choker from the Rigi set and the Madison bra and garter belt and I just love how
everything looks together and I think the really extravagant point that takes
it to the next level are the red edges because you can see them still so it's
just a hint of red but it gives it such a cool vibe and I love the combination
of red black and gold here so yeah this is really cool looks totally badass and
and i love how everything is size adjustable i'm wearing size small and you can really
push it a bit and tighten it wherever you want to and support your body shape with tightening
the right straps in the right places with the cuffs and choco there also come these linking
parts so you can put this one here for example. Well, okay, doing this alone, we have to do
the other way around first here and now here. Alright, so you can either join the cuffs
Or you could join the garter belt or the harness.
And I have to emphasize again that the metal parts are really cool with all the engravings.
And I think it's really like a rosé gold almost.
Because it looks so tone and tone a bit with the red.
I don't know. It's just gorgeous.
And you can play around with it.
Now this is like the version where everything comes together. A sheer bodysuit,
a lot of harder stuff. But I want to show you a toned down everyday version so I'm
going to change the casual look so to say. If you don't want to go full out
there with just a sheer mesh body, why not dress it like that with a coat of jeans
and use the bodysuit as a top and just the leather bra part and you can totally
go on like that in a bar. I also took apart the cuffs and yeah just put it here as a
kind of accessory keychain to pull everything a bit together because maybe
I could add a belt or whatever but I love this look it's really cool but
casual. Next up is a lingerie set so even less fabric. Tada! The crystal lingerie set.
Marimou does not only make harnesses and bodysuits but also they have a great
range of lingerie and some really unique designs so check them out. And this is a
a three-piece set I decided on. It's super cool with all the different parts that work together
as a whole again and you can also adjust every strap even the ones here in the neck which is
really cool so there's not too much tension going on here it fits really great also with the panties
adjusting them and I'm glad that the garter belt is here because it adds a bit of fabric again to
the panty there's really not much in front but better from the back and yeah the design of the
bra is really outstanding I think it would look cool under a normal top so you can see this part
here as kind of lingerie harness I don't know so I think you can totally combine it with
normal clothing to add that little extra again for the next outfit the last harness I brought
a catsuit from home because I wanted to show you like a whole bunch of combination possibilities
so let's go I'm getting changed I think I just found my next party outfit for my next Finnish party
because this is BAM! Like I don't know it's like in your face. With the gold it really screams like
look at me look at me and it's an eyecatcher for sure. Also the combination with the black is always
like really elegant and I think with the matte catsuit you kind of draw the eye even more to the
shiny leather parts and the chain parts here. So this is called the Goldini set.
How fitting.
It's so cool.
Totally love it. I don't know, you can't really compare it to the first harness I think
because this is like more jewelry than a normal harness with all the chains and
all the gold and the first one was a bit more toned down but also cool i don't know i i can't
decide between them luckily i have both so on the product pictures from my mom i saw that they
combined the set with lingerie lacy sheer lingerie which also looks great but i want to try something
different and do it with the catsuit and i think it's also look i like it so much
I know a lot of guys watch my videos so hint hint these boxes make great gifts to your girlfriend
your wife your I don't know beloved one so I think if you like gift something like this and
their quality it's definitely better than the next door H&M luxury set probably
because this is just wow and I think it's a great gift idea. Just saying.
I showed you like one, two, three, four looks today. Or was it four? I don't know.
And I hope you liked them. I hope you enjoyed this video. Tell me in the
comments down below which of the outfits was your favorite. Also leave a thumbs up
and subscribe to my channel and all that stuff. Check out the Marie Mouer page. I'll link
everything down below in the description text. And I have a discount code. I'll also leave
the discount code below. And I hope you're having a nice day. See you in the next video. Bye!